football. That's all I know. Ball ball.
That's all I want to do, man.
>> After the 2024 ACL injury, looks like
you bounced back last year a little bit.
Do you feel like you're moving back
toward becoming the player you were or
having the production you had in 20, you
know, as a freshman and sophomore?
>> No doubt. I feel like um I gained my
confidence back in my knee. I feel like
I did everything I was supposed to do
rehabilitation wise for me to have all
the confidence in the roll and go out
there and play. So yeah, most definitely
to answer your question.
>> Harold, how do you kind of when you
think about your career at LSU,
highs, lows, how do you look at it? How
do you think about it?
>> Um, I feel like it it it went how it was
supposed to go. Um, that's something
that I learned while I was there. You
know, everybody want the perfect
Cinderella story, but it ain't always
like that. It ain't always be p peaches
and cream. You know, my plan when I came
to college was to go to the league in
three years and graduate in three years,
>> but God had other plans for me. So, uh
that's what that was. I just had to
accept that and know
>> that God is real and um he got me.
>> My plans ain't always what God has
planned for me.
>> They talk to you a little bit about what
kind of role they see you playing here
in Atlanta. I know you're you can do a
lot of different things, but I mean,
have they talked to you a little bit
about any any specifics like that?
>> No, nothing specific. Um, I'm pretty
sure they know I'm versatile. You know,
they they they would have came got me if
they didn't think they could do nothing
with me. I'm just excited to get my feet
in the building and work me.
>> What's something that you think that you
could bring to this team, to this
defense next season?
>> Versatility.
Okay.
>> Do you anticipate playing edge or
linebacker or a little bit of both?
>> Um, when I was when I was doing my
process, I told every team I met with, I
felt like I was the most versatile
player in the draft. I feel like I could
do a little bit of everything. So, felt
like they caught my drift. That's why
they came and got me. They obviously
seen some seen see something, you know.
>> Yep.
>> Harold. um you were saying what you were
saying about,
you know, kind of understanding not
everyone has a Cinderella story and and
things are working out where they're
supposed to. I feel like it's a really
mature way of looking at it. Was there
anyone in particular that helped you
look at it that way? Kind of view it in
that in that lens.
>> Uh not really. I would say I'm just very
in tune with my emotions. I'm very
realistic with myself, you know. Of
course, everybody want to be a first
round draft pick. Everybody want to go
to number one overall, but that's just
not how it go for everybody. You know,
that's one person.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you just got to know at the end of
the day, it ain't where you start, it's
how it's about how you finish, right?
>> You know, this was my this wasn't my
goal. My end goal anyways. My end goal
wasn't just to get to the league. You
know, my end goal is to have a gold
jacket.
>> Wow.
>> This just part of my story.
>> But I'm very excited though. It's a big
chapter.
>> Yeah. Can you you you're saying you you
feel more confident in a knee now. Can
you describe just maybe where you were
last fall?
>> Oh yeah. I'm a dirty bird.
>> Hey, this don't feel real though. If I
tell yall one thing, it don't feel real.
It still kind of hit me right now.
>> Can you describe like just how you feel
with your knee now compared to maybe
even a few months ago or or when you
first were cleared?
>> I'm good. Me and my knee, we structure.
We good. You know, like we good. I'm
confident in my knee and myself as well.
Like, you know, like I said before, um I
felt like I did everything I was
supposed to do in my in my
rehabilitation process. I I soon as I
could hit the ground and started
running, that's what I did.
And I ain't no days off. I actually put
extra work in, too. So, I felt like I
had I had all the confidence in a row to
go out there and ball for real.
Are you at home right now?
>> Yeah, I'm celebrating with with the fam.
>> Yeah. What's I mean I I I Can you kind
of put into words what you describe a
little bit about just just how excited
and and eager you are to to get going
and start this new chapter?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm super excited. I'm
excited. I'm anxious. I say that I say
that's that's the that's that's really
how I'm feeling right there. The two
biggest words that describe how I'm
feeling. I'm excited and I'm anxious to
get going.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, just because I felt like I
know it ain't 200 people in this draft
better than me for one. I know that for
a fact. But that's what I use as my
motivation to go get it.
>> Is that So, is that a chip on your
shoulder that you you're taking where
you were?
>> I always I'm always have a chip on my
shoulder. You know, I feel like that
that you got to always chase something.
Can't just get up every morning, you
know, without a chip on your shoulder
just thinking, you know, however you
thinking. I most definitely feel like I
got a chip on my shoulder. Always have,
always will.
>> Harold, uh, can I ask you about the the
elephant in the room? Did you grow up a
Saints fan?
>> Yeah, I grew up a Saints fan.
>> Hey, guess what though?
>> I ain't a Saints fan no more.